This is a camera worth ₹1500 and this is a camera worth ₹1,30,000.
So I've been
making videos on YouTube for the past 4 years and have
used almost every type of vlogging camera, but which one
is the best?  So the first thing I used was
a DSL R which was really great.
Nice background blur and photos that can
become posters.  The only problem with this camera was its
weight.  Firstly, you cannot hold it in your hand and
block it for long.  And secondly, whenever you
go anywhere, you have to
carry two-three lenses along with the camera in your bag.
Then to solve these problems
I bought GoPro.  I took this camera with me
into the snow.  Took it into the water.  It
even flew and was
so small that I could vlog nonstop.
But the problem was with its video
quality.  I myself was not enjoying watching it.
So then I thought that since there is so much
talk about iPhone, let's
buy one and I swear on ostriches.  This
phone changed my life.  Now because I
make most of the shots.  The quality
went from ground to seventh heaven.  But the
problem was with storage and battery which was
causing 5 grams of trouble in my day to day life.
Then the brand sent me this insta
360x5 which is such an advanced camera that it
shoots 360°.  Meaning, I, the
sky and the earth, all three brothers in one frame, this is a complete Kalakand
camera.  But the biggest problem with this was that
every clip had to be reframed for editing,
which wasted a lot of time.
Then I bought just a month ago
this DJI pocket camera with gimbal and
107 GB internal storage.  Moreover, it is
so compact that it fits in my pocket
and the best part is that I already had the
DJI mic which
connects directly to the Bluetooth face without any receiver.
But it is not that there is
no problem in this.  It's just the best for my [music] use
right now, and
we use our iPhone every day as well.
As for this Rs 1500 camera,
I bought it just for fun.  Slow